

# Kody **Brown**

Software Architect

### **CONTACT ME**



(801) 310-1122



kody@vutiliti.com vutiliti.com



KE7ZIU



7065 S 5490 W West Jordan, UT 84081

### LINKS

GitHub, LinkedIn, Twitter, G+, FB kodybrown

**SKYPE** 

wasatchwizard

**WEB** 

kodybrown.com wasatchwizard.com

### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

| UI/UX Design   |
|----------------|
| HTML5          |
| CSS3           |
| JavaScript     |
| Responsive Web |
| C# / ASP.NET   |



### **ABOUT ME**

I am passionate about technology in all of its various forms. From running a large network of Bitcoin miners, building go-karts and electric scooters, playing with amateur (ham) radio, to converting a 40-foot school bus to a mobile hacker station and RV for the family. I am exceptionally skilled across the full stack of software development and Internet of Things (IoT) devices.

I take pride in transforming complex challenges into simple and elegant solutions, while maintaining an intuitive user experience. I can focus on the big picture while pacing myself and teams through the iterative development process, ensuring stable and extendable solutions.



### **EDUCATION**

**Business Management University of Phoenix** 

2002 - 2003

Robotics & Fabrication, Software Engineering Modesto Junior College

1992 - 1994



### **BUZZWORTHY**

#### Graduated high school early

Graduated high school at 15 years old and started attending college.

#### Essential C#

One of the technical editors of (three editions of) the Essential C# book by Mark Michaelis.

#### Patent #8,275,895

Steve Ellis and I are co-authors of "DHCP – Systems and methods for establishing a trusted dynamic host configuration protocol connection."

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Vutiliti, Inc. Web Architect

2015 - Present

Created responsive, mobile-first website using Angular.js and back-end services in ASP.NET Web API and Go. Worked with partners to solve enterprise issues using custom hardware and software to save our customers money.

ConsultNet 2013 - 2016

### Web Architect (Consultant)

Created responsive websites using Angular.js, Sitecore CMS, Node, Meteor, PhoneGap, Ember.js, and ASP.NET MVC while constantly adjusting to different teams, environments, and schedules.

Venafi, Inc. 2008 - 2013

#### Web Architect

Led a team of six developers in the design and implementation of a webbased PKI management console for Fortune 100 companies. Worked closely with the UI/UX lead to create a stunning and extremely friendly user interface. I also focused a majority of my time on XSS and CSRF prevention.

#### OneGreatFamily.com Web Architect

2006 - 2008

Led a team of four developers in creating a web-based genealogy website, including an online family tree, extensible dashboard, and widgets.

### LANDesk Software, Inc. Senior Software Engineer

Worked on the ISV team in different areas of development. From Classic ASP to C#/ASP.NET, and Windows CE/Mobile (C++) and BlackBerry (J2ME) devices. Created LANDesk Message-based SDK and Handheld Manager (which had over 1 million client installs).